Sean Klein

seanrk06@icloud.com

Skills

Skilled in project management, data analytics, and team leadership. I also possess knowledge of a multitude of programming languages, including but not limited to Python, C, and Javascript. With those languages I have accumulated experience and am now able to build full-stack web applications using multiple frameworks within the aforementioned languages. You can find more information on that here https://seanklein.info/.

Experience

June 2019 - August 2019

Counselor In Training -

• Helped supervise a group of kids for a Summer under the leadership of a head counselor.

June 2021 - August 2021

Taco Bell - Service Champion

- Worked as a cashier for both the drive-through and front register.
- Oversaw customers' meals from the kitchen in order to make sure they received their complete order

June 2021 - August 2021

Neurology Practice Assistant -

- Managed data relating to patient records in research involving migraine patients.
- Oversaw patient-facing facilities and made sure equipment was maintained properly.
- Cataloged medication for study subjects.

June 2022 - August 2022

Busser -

59 Almshouse Rd, Richboro, PA 18954

 Addressed service-related needs of the customers in addition to team support of coworkers.

Education

Date of Graduation: 2024

High School -

- 4.2 Weighted GPA
- Business Courses:
 - Accelerated Personal Finance
 - Introduction to Entrepreneurship

- AP Courses
 - AP United States History
 - Received a 5 on the National AP Test
 - AP English Lang
 - AP Psychology
 - AP European History
 - AP Computer Science Principles
- Clubs
 - Technology Club
 - President as of August 2022
 - o Ski and Snowboard Club
 - Aug 2019 -
 - Roe Kappa Social Studies Honors Society
 - Oct. 2022 -
 - NASA Hunch Club
 - Aug. 2021 -
 - Co-leader on a team whose goal was designing a Insect Nano Containment Box prototype to be potentially used on the ISS
 - Computer Science Club
 - Aug. 2021 Jun. 2021
 - Jewish Heritage Society
 - Aug. 2022 -
 - Model United Nations
 - Aug. 2021 -
 - o Future Business Leaders of America (FBLA)
 - Aug. 2022 -

Awards

- Received two honorable mention awards for my project Refuge For Ukraine which can be found here https://devpost.com/software/refuge-for-ukraine
- Received business student of the month for exemplary work (May 2022)
- Inducted into Roe Kappa honors society

Outside of School Extracurriculars

- Sigma Alpha Rho fraternity
 - President of Phi Chapter as of Jan. 2021
 - Sigma Alpha Roe is a student-run youth organization with thousands of alumni whose primary goal is to instill a sense of leadership and values in young men.
 - In my time as president I more than doubled the size of our group from 8 to 20 and we plan to continue to expand.
- Volunteering

I have committed over 50 hours to a local market that supports healthy soil,
 produce, pastures, animals, people, and local communities.

Programming

- Website Development
 - Personal Portfolio Website (https://seanklein.info/)
 - I built this website to display my achievements and my recent projects to act as a "virtual resume."
 - Technology Club Website (https://technologyclub.netlify.app/)
 - I built this website for a club I am the co-president of whose goal is to increase student understanding of modern technology through discussion groups, demonstrations, and hands-on experiences. It was not submitted for a competition.
 - RefugeForUkraine Website

(https://devpost.com/software/refuge-for-ukraine)

- This award-winning website was designed to track the Russia-Ukraine War visually to send help where it's most needed.
- ForgetMeNot Website

(https://devpost.com/software/forget-me-not-93xuw2)

- Teachers and students alike have struggled with virtual learning since the start of the pandemic. This website can help with the productivity of students and the management of teachers.
- Study Buddy Website (https://devpost.com/software/study-buddy-rit0sq)
 - The Covid-19 pandemic has increased anxiety globally. Study
 Buddy was made to help young adults cope with social anxiety. It is
 not hosted live.
- Courses I've taken
 - The Complete 2022 Web Development Bootcamp by Dr. Angela Yu